<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/00wip-cybersecurity-lecture-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/00wip-cybersecurity-lecture-overview/</guid>
      <description>TODOS&#xA;continue flushing out the core knowledge figure out a way to put everything into a single file and run through ai to check for dups and reorganize. DATA STRUCTURE Modularized so that each page can be independently expanded.&#xA;DESIGN PRINCIPALS&#xA;efficient, utilitarian, LGBTQIA+ themed (lesbian and trans colors) open source and transparent, a focus on truth, honesty and anti greed [[Tech Resources and Cybersecurity Hub Website Schema]]&#xA;[[Personal Knowledge Management and Leveraging AI Tools in work and personal life]]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about-page/</guid>
      <description>About Page About the Workshop Meet your instructors and learn about our mission at the Ali Forney Center - 307 W 38th St FL 3.&#xA;Hosted by: Calyx Padgett and Unity Works.&#xA;Instructor&amp;rsquo;s Bio: Calyx brings expertise from a Computer Science background at Rose-Hulman and personal insights from the cybersecurity field, aiming to empower individuals with the knowledge to protect their digital lives.&#xA;About Ali Forney Center: Dedicated to LGBTQ+ youth, the center provides a safe space for learning and personal growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/for-other-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/for-other-developers/</guid>
      <description>https://github.com/emberauclair/Tech-Hub-V5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/homepage/</guid>
      <description>Home Page Welcome to My Tech Resources Learn to protect your digital life effectively. Join us for an engaging workshop where you&amp;rsquo;ll learn the essentials of protecting your digital presence.&#xA;What You Will Learn: Understanding Cyber Threats: Explore how AI and quantum computing shape modern cybersecurity threats. Essential Tools: Learn to secure your passwords against AI-powered attacks using tools like Bitwarden. DiceWare: Create robust, yet memorable passwords. Phishing Awareness: Identify and avoid deceptive phishing attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/learning-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/learning-ai/</guid>
      <description>AI Learning Page and applications Welcome to the exciting world of Artificial Intelligence (AI)! AI is a transformative force in technology, capable of processing and analyzing data at speeds incomprehensible to the human mind. Here, we explore how you can harness AI to enhance your creativity, decision-making, and productivity, especially in fields like web development, text handling, coding, brainstorming, planning, and management.&#xA;Why AI? AI offers unparalleled efficiency and can assist in complex tasks including:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/personal-knowledge-management-and-leveraging-ai-tools-in-work-and-personal-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/personal-knowledge-management-and-leveraging-ai-tools-in-work-and-personal-life/</guid>
      <description>Personal Knowledge Management and AI Tools Obsidian Description: A free personal knowledge base that adapts to your thinking style, supporting how you think and process information. Features: Stores everything in plaintext, facilitating easy copy and paste interactions between AI tools and Obsidian, making it highly adaptable for personal use. Website: Obsidian Zettlekasten Method Overview: Focuses on manipulating blocks of text rather than individual words. This method enhances the structure and accessibility of information, allowing for more effective knowledge management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/phishing-awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/phishing-awareness/</guid>
      <description>Phishing Awareness Understanding the landscape of scams and how to protect oneself is crucial. This page covers top scams, financial exploitation, cognitive behavior, types of scams, tools used in scams, and more.&#xA;Top Local Scams in 2024 Geek squad account takeovers Amazon customer support fraud Virus protection scams Mail theft Grocery store distractions Compromised bank accounts Federal investigation schemes Wire transfer fraud Computer Scams Awareness of the various forms of computer scams is key to protecting yourself and your assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/wip-cybersecurity-workshop-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/wip-cybersecurity-workshop-page/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Page Practical Cybersecurity and the Threat of AI and Quantum Computing A basic and practical lecture on how to stay safe, protect your privacy, and keep from being hacked.&#xA;Instructor Qualifications: 2 years at Rose-Hulman for Computer Science. Insight from Cyber Security for Rolls Royce&amp;rsquo;s Jet Engines, experience at 2 different startups, and government contracting.&#xA;Tools and Resources: Free Password Manager - Bitwarden DiceWare for Generating Secure Passwords SurfSharkVpn - keeps you safe online Phishing Attacks: Understand what it is, why it matters, and how to protect yourself.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
